A Guide to the Fries Textile Plant Records, 1900-1988
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II: Correspondence, 1901-1958
  - Mystic Adhesive Products, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - New Jersey Zink Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - North Carolina State College, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - North Electric Company, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous "O", 1956 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - O'Hanlon-Watson Drug Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Oil City Gas Co., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous "P", 1956 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Parks-Cramer Company, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Paul Knitting Mills, Inc., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Penick and Ford, Ltd, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Piedmont Mountian Freight Lines, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - R.P. Johnson Sons, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - St. Louis Button Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Leslie Evans and Co., April 1941 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Leslie Evans and Co. - May, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Leslie Evans and Co. - June, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Leslie Evans and Co. - July, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Leslie Evans and Co., August 1941 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Leslie Evans And Co., September 1941 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous "M", 1942 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - JW Mantell Company, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Maryland Casualty Co., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - The Mathieson Alkali Works, Inc., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - McGriffin and Company, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Mente and Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Merchants Nation Company, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Morton Manufacturing Company, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Miscellaneous "N", 1942 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Nashville Bag and Burlap Co., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - National Electric Coil Co., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Dr. Herbert H Neisser MD, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Nelson Hardware Company, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway Company, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Miscellaneous "O", 1942 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Odell Mill Supply Co., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Miscellaneous "P", 1942 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Park, Davis and Co., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Park Manufacturing Company, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Peck, Stow and Wilcox Co., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Postmaster, G.K. Fielder, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Miscellaneous R, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Radford Limestone Co., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Railway Mail Service, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Revolution Cotton Mills, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - J.E. Rhoods and Sons, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Richmond Machinery and Equipment Co., Inc., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Riverside and Dan River Cotton Mills, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Riverside Mills, Inc., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Roberts Filter Mfg. Co., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Rock Hill Ptg. and Fin. Co., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Rock Run Mills, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Royal Mfg. Co., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Miscellaneous "S", 1942 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Salem Foundry and Machine Works,Inc., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Saunders and Mader, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - J.W. Scott and Company, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Service Appliance Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - James W. Seville, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Seydel Chemical Company, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Seydel-Woolley and Company, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Signode Steel Strapping Company, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Slip-Not Belting Corporation, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - S. Morgan Smith Company, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - E.E. Smith and Son, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Social Security Board, 1942 (Box 155, Folder 28)
  - Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Sonoco Products Company, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Southern Converting Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Southern Oxygen Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Southern Shuttles, Inc. (See also Steel Heddle Mfg. Co.), 1942 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Southern Spindle and Flyer Co., Inc., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Southern Standard Mill Supply, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Southern Weighing and Inspection, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Southwestern Inc., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Spaugh Paper Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - A.E. Staley Mfg. Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Standard Oil Company, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Steel Heddle Mfg. Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Stein, Hall and Company, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Superior Sterling Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - H.C. Swann, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Swift and Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous "T", 1942 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Taylor Investment Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - The Terrell Machine Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Textile Mill Supply Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - The Fidesley Coal Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Timber Engineering Company, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Traffic Dept. I, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Traffic Dept. II, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - United Fruit Co., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - US Army and Navy War Board, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Bays in MIlitary Service - U.S. Government, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - US Govt. - W.P.B., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Eclipse Mill Crayon Co., 1922 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Eco Clock Co., 1920-1921 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Economy Engineering Co., 1918 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Economy Pumping and Machinery Co., 1920-1922 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Edwards Manufacturing Co., 1919-1922 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Efird Mfg. Company (S.D. Bennett), 1920 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Electric Controller and Manufacturing, 1918-1922 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Electric Equipment Co. of America, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Electric Machinery Mfg. Co., 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Electrical World, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Mr. Frank Elkins, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Elliott Co., 1918 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - B.K. Elliott Co., 1918-1919 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Emmert Mfg. Co., 1921 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Emmons Loom Harness Co., 1918-1921 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Engleby Bros. Co., 1922 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Enterprise Cooperage, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - T.C. Entwistle Co., 1920-1922 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Eureka Coal Co., 1919-1922 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Herbert Evans, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Everlasbestos Flooring Co., 1922 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Everwear Mftg Co., 1922 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - S.F. Ewald Insurance Agency, 1918-1922 (Box 155, Folder 29)
  - Ezell Griffin Co., 1920 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Miscellaneous "F", 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Factory Insurance Association, 1921-1922 (Box 155, Folder 30)
  - Fafnir Bearing Co., 1918-1922 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Fairbanks Co., 1918-1922 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Fairbanks Morse and Co., 1921 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Fairfield Engineering Works, 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Falconer Co., 1918-1922 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Fales and Jenks Machine Co., 1920-1922 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Fall River Bleachery, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - W.L. Farmer, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Farmers Supply Co., 1919 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - C.D. Farnham, 1918-1919 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Faunt Leroy Elevator Co., 1918 (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Federal Electric Co., 1918-1922 (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Federal Fuel Administrator, 1918-1919 (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Fenton Label Co., 1918-1920 (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - John W. Ferguson Co., 1918-1920 (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Ferrubron Metal Paint Co., 1918 (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - M.F. Field, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - Files Engineering Co., 1919 (Box 22, Folder 86)
  - Fields Hash Mfg. Co., 1920 (Box 22, Folder 87)
  - Financial Daily America, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 88)
  - Mr. G.M. Finley, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 89)
  - Fire Protectin Survey Bureau, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 90)
  - William Firth, 1917-1919 (Box 22, Folder 91)
  - First National Bank- Parkersburg, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 92)
  - Frank E. Fitts Mgr. and Supply Company, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 93)
  - Mr. R.G. Fitzhugh, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 94)
  - Flat Top Fuel Co., 1918-1922 (Box 22, Folder 95)
  - Foamite Fire Foam Co., 1920 (Box 22, Folder 96)
  - Ford, Bacon and Davis, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 97)
  - Mrs. WT Foreman, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 98)
  - Geo. W. Forrester (folder 1 of 3), 1922 (Box 22, Folder 99)
  - Geo. W. Forrester (folder 2 of 3), 1922 (Box 22, Folder 100)
  - Geo. W. Forrester (folder 3 of 3), 1922 (Box 22, Folder 101)
  - Geo W Forrester Traffic Mgr, 1921 (Box 22, Folder 102)
  - Fort Dearborn Coal Co., 1918-1919 (Box 22, Folder 103)
  - Fort Wayne Corrugated Paper Co., 1919 (Box 22, Folder 104)
  - Fortune Hunter Coal Co., 1919 (Box 22, Folder 105)
  - Foster Machine Co., 1921 (Box 22, Folder 106)
  - Foster Milburn Co., 1919 (Box 22, Folder 107)
  - William Foster Jr., 1920 (Box 22, Folder 108)
  - Fox Supply Co., 1922 (Box 22, Folder 109)
  - Foxboro Co, Inc., 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 110)
  - CorFranklin Pen Co., 1920 (Box 22, Folder 111)
  - Franklin Supply Co., 1922 (Box 22, Folder 112)
  - Frederick Disinfectant Co., 1918 (Box 22, Folder 113)
  - E.M. Freese and Co., 1919 (Box 22, Folder 114)
  - Frick Co., 1921 (Box 22, Folder 115)
  - Frictioned Roller Cloth Co., 1921 (Box 22, Folder 116)
  - Col. F.H. Fries, President, 1918-1922 (Box 22, Folder 117)
  - Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills, 1919-1921 (Box 22, Folder 118)
  - Mr. J.W. Fulton, 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 119)
  - W.B. Fulton, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 120)
  - Funk and Wagnalls, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 121)
  - Furr Construction Co., 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 122)
  - Fyans, Fraser, and Blackway Co., 1919-1921 (Box 22, Folder 123)
  - John Eichleay Jr. Co., 1919 (Box 22, Folder 124)
  - C.L. Upchurch and Sons, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 125)
  - Dept. of Commerce, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 126)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 127)
  - US Govt. Office of Price Administration, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 128)
  - US Govt., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 129)
  - Leslie Evans and Company, January 1942 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Leslie Evans and Company, February 1942 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Leslie Evans and Company, 1942, March (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - H.F. Livermore Co.; Lloveras Comp. Inc; C.E. Luttrell and Comp.; Lynchburg Iron and Metal, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - US Priorities (folder 1 of 2), 1942 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - US Priorities (folder 2 of 2), 1942 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - US Ring Traveler Co., 1942 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous V, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Veeder-Root Incorporated, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Assoc., 1942 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Virginia O.C.D., 1942 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Virginia State Wide Safety Conference, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - VA Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1942 (Box 155, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous "W", 1942 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Wallace and Tiernan Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Waltham Watch Co., 1942 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Werthan Bag Corporation, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Westbrook Elevation and Mfg. Co., 1942 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Western Marine Express, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Westinghouse Elec. and Mfg. Co., 1942 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Westinghouse Elec. Supply Co., 1942 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Troy Whitehead Machinery Company, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - The Whitehead and Hoag Company, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Whitin Machine Works, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous "Y", 1942 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous "Z", 1942 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Corresp., 1942 (Box 155, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous A, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Abbott Machine Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Abington Textile Machinery Works; Acme Steel Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - A.C. Blancke and Co.; A.P. Bond Paper Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Acme Steale Corp; York Corp; Yarnall-Waring Comp., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Addison, Clarke and Bros.; Addressograph Sales Agency, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Air Reduction Sales Co.; E. Ellwood Allen Organization, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - American Coal Co.; American Associated Consultants, Inc., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - American Cooperage and Steel Drum Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - American Cotton Manufacturing Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - American-Hawaiian Steamship Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - American Manufacturing Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - American Monorail Co. (folder 1 of 2), 1947-48 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - American Monorail Co. (folder 2 of 2), 1947-48 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - American National Bag and Burlap Co.; American Photocopy Equipment Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - American Playground Device Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Amsterdam Print and Lithograph Co.; Ansul Chemical Co., 1946-47 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Appalachian Electric Power Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Armour and Company; Armstrong Cork Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Arrow Steamship Line; Ashworth Bros., Inc., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Atlanta Bag and Burlap Co.; Atlanta Brush Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Atlas Supply Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - A.W. Cash Co.; C. Grady Cates, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous B., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Bahan Textile Machinery Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - The Bahnson Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Bahnson, Spaugh, Reid, Etc. -- [Washington Mills, Winston-Salem, NC.], 1947 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Barber-Colman Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Belk Department Stores, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Belknap Hardware Manufacturing Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Bemis Bros. Bag Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Borne Scrymser Company; J.J. Bower Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Boye and Emmes Machine Tool Co.; Bright Brooks Lumber Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Britton Corporation, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Frank E Brown, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Butler Iron and Steel Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Miscellaneous C., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Caldwell Cinder Block Co.; T.A. Canity, Inc., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Carolina Bagging Co.; Carroll County Officials, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - C.E. Craver and Son; E.F Craven Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Celotex Corporation; Charlotte Salvage Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Chicago Pharmical Company; City Sales Company, Inc., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Clinchfield Fuel Co.; Clipper Manufacturing Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Clover Manufacturing Company; C-O Two Fire Equipment Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Cochrane Corporation, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Cohoes Iron Foundry and Machine Co.; Corn Products Sales Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Cotton; Cotton-Textile Institute, Inc., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Crucible Steel Company of America; Crystal Springs Bleachery, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Currier-Withers Supply Company; Curtis and Marble Machine Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Cutters Exchange, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Miscellaneous D., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Dan River Mills; D. and S. Engineering Company, 1942-1947 (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Dillard Paper Company; Divine Bros., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 81)
  - Dixie Bag Company; R.L. Dixon and Bros., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - W.D Dodenhoff Company; Dodge Manufacturing Co., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Drake Corporation, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 84)
  - Draper Corporation, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - Miscellaneous E, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - E.F. Houghton and Company; Hunt Loom Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 87)
  - E.H. Jacobs Manufacturing Corp.; Jenkins Metal Shop, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 88)
  - Ernest F. Culbreath Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 89)
  - Miscellaneous F, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 90)
  - Factory Insurance Association, 1947 (Box 155, Folder 33)
  - Fastener Corporation; Faultless Caster Corporation, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 92)
  - [Fries] First National Bank; Flowers School Equipment Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 93)
  - Michael Flynn Manufacturing Co.; Fries, Town of, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 94)
  - Fuller Brush Company, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 95)
  - Miscellaneous G, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - A.F. Gallun and Sons Corp.; General Electric Supply Corp., 1947 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - General Motor Lines, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Giant Manufacturing Company; Clair H. Gingher, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Gossett Machine Works, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - W.E. Graham and Sons; Gravely Potomac, Inc., 1947 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Grayson County; Grayson Garment Factory, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Hobert N. Grubb, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - W. and L.E. Gurley, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous H, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - H. and P. Spool and Bobbin Company; Charles J. Haas, Inc., 1947 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Haas-Miller Corporation; Hardwood Manufacturing Co., 1947 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Haynes Stellite Company; N.B. Hnady Company, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - John D. Hollingsworth on Wheels, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Hospital Savings Association, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous I, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Ideal Machine Shops, Inc.; Independent Lock Company, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Industrial Chemical and Supply, Inc.; Industrial Supply Company, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Intercommunication System of America; International Business Machines (IBM) Corporation, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous J, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - John Bayne and Company, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - R.P. Johnson Company, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous K, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Kalamazoo Tank and Silo Company; Kearney and Trecker Company, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Kemble Cochrane Company; Kennametal, Inc., 1947 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Kester Machinery Company; Kingsport Electric Company, Inc., 1947 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Knox Glass Associates, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous C, 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous C, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous C, 1918-1921 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Calcutta Burlap Co., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Calkins Dredging Co. Inc., 1922 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - D.W. Call, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Cameron Bandage Slitting and Rewinding Machine Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - A.S. Cameron Steam Pump Works, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Campbell Mfg. Co., 1920-1922 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Stuart B. Campbell, 1918-1919 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Cannelton Sewer Pipe Co., 1920 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Carbolineum Wood Preserving Co., 1920 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Cardwell Machine Co., 1920-1921 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Carey Machine and Supply Company, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Philip Carey Co., 1919-1921 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Carnegie Steel Company, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Carolina Bagging Co., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Carolina Foundry and Machine Co., 1918-1922 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Carolina States Electric Co., 1922 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Carolina Steel Roller Shop, 1920-1921 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Carolina Supply Co., 1918-1921 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Geo. B. Carpenter Co., 1920 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - W.B. Carpenter Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Carrier Engineering Corp., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Carroll County Officials, 1920-1922 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Carroll Electric Co., 1920 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Mr. E Carson, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - A.B. Carter, 1918-1922 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Cartwright Metal Roofing Co., 1922 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - B. Cassell and Co., 1920 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - R.A. Cawthorn Paper Co., 1919-1920 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Central Construction and Supply Co., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Central Foundry Co., 1919-1920 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Central Foundry Machine and Works, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - C.H. and E. Mfg Co. Inc., 1920 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Thomas K. Chaffee Co., 1920-1921 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Chapman Mfg. Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Charlotte Leather Belting Co., 1918-1921 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Charlotte Mfg Co., 1918-1922 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Charlotte Supply Co., 1918-1922 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - The Chatfield and Woods Co, 1922 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Chattanooga Sewer Pipe Works, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Cherokee Ochre Co., 1919 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Chesapeke and Virginia Coal Co., 1918-1922 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Chicago Fuse Mfg. Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Chicago Pneumatic Tool Co., 1922 (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Chicago Watchman, Clock Wks., 1918-1921 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Cincinatti Elec. Tool Co., 1920-1922 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Cincinatti Elevator Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Cincinatti Refrigerating Mchy. Co., 1920-1921 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Cincinatti Time Clock Co., 1919 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Clarence Cosby, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Clark Fuel Co., 1918-1920 (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - H.E. Clark Mfg. Co., 1918-1919 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Clayton and Bentley Co., 1919-1921 (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Clear Creek Coal Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Clements-Nesom Lumber Co., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - [Clevland] Pneumatic Tool Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - [Clevland] Stoker and Mfg. Co., 1919 (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - [Clevland] Twist Drill Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Henry Clews and Co., 1919 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Clinchfield Fuel Co., 1918-1922 (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Cocker Machine and Foundry Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Cohoes Iron Foundry and Machine Co., 1919-1923 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Cokal Stoker Co., 1919 (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - Colonial Mfg. Co., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Colorcraft Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Columbia Ironworks, 1918-1919 (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - Columbia Metal Box Co., 1920 (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - Columbia Postal Supply Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - Columbia Steel and Shafting Co., 1919-1921 (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - J.F. Coodedge and Sons, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - Cook and Co., 1921-1922 (Box 24, Folder 100)
  - Commerce and Finance, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 101)
  - Commercial Travelers Mutual Accident Association of Am., 1920 (Box 24, Folder 102)
  - Concrete Reinforcing and Engineering Co., 1919 (Box 24, Folder 103)
  - Concrete Steel Co., 1921 (Box 24, Folder 104)
  - Congoleum Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 105)
  - Consolidated Belting Co., 1919 (Box 24, Folder 106)
  - Consolidated Color and Chemical Co., 1918-1921 (Box 24, Folder 107)
  - Consumers Paper Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 108)
  - Cooper and Griffin, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 109)
  - Co-Operative Fuel Co., 1920-1922 (Box 24, Folder 110)
  - Cordley and Hayes, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 111)
  - Cornell and Underhill, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 112)
  - Mr. M.O. Cornett, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 113)
  - Corresp., 1919-1921 (Box 24, Folder 114)
  - Cotton Mftr. Assoc. of N.C., 1918-1922 (Box 24, Folder 115)
  - S.H. Couch Co. Inc., 1921 (Box 24, Folder 116)
  - Dana S Courtney Co., 1919-1922 (Box 24, Folder 117)
  - Mr. John Cox, Medical Dept. UVA, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 118)
  - Bruce V. Crandall, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 119)
  - Crandall Packing Co, 1920-1921 (Box 24, Folder 120)
  - Crane Co., 1919 (Box 24, Folder 121)
  - L.G. Crenshaw Coal Co., 1918-1922 (Box 24, Folder 122)
  - Crescent Mch. Co., 1920 (Box 24, Folder 123)
  - Crescent Paper Mills, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 124)
  - [Cresent] Paper Tube Co., 1920 (Box 24, Folder 125)
  - Cresson-Morris Company, 1919-1922 (Box 24, Folder 126)
  - Samuel J Creswell Iron Works, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 127)
  - Crockett Red Ash Coal Co., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 128)
  - Lewis A Crossett Inc, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 129)
  - R.W. Croxton, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 130)
  - Con. P. Curran Printing Co., 1922 (Box 24, Folder 131)
  - Curt Teich and Co., 1922 (Box 24, Folder 132)
  - Curtis and Marble Machine Co., 1918-1922 (Box 24, Folder 133)